A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 6: Subject Files
  - Subseries 3: Subject Files, 1927-1946
    - F.E.R.A. - Richmond, 1934-35 (Box-folder 41-2247)
    - F.E.R.A., 1934-35 (Box-folder 42-2248)
    - F.E.R.A. - Payroll, Student Help, 1934-35 (Box-folder 42-2249)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1936 (Box-folder 42-2250)
      - Regulations Concerning the National Housing Act.
    - Federal Income Taxes, 1937-41 (Box-folder 42-2251)
    - Committee on Financial Aid, 1943 (Box-folder 42-2252)
    - Financial Documents & Reports, 1941-42 (Box-folder 42-2253)
    - Forestry, 1930-34 (Box-folder 42-2254)
    - Forestry Conference, VA Commercial at Richmond, 2/11/1930 (Box-folder 42-2255)
    - Form Letters, 1934 (Box-folder 42-2256)
    - General Assembly, 1933-34 (Box-folder 42-2257)
    - General Assembly, 1936 (Box-folder 42-2258)
    - General Assembly, 1938 (Box-folder 42-2259)
    - General Assembly, 1940 (Box-folder 42-2260)
    - General Assembly, 1944 (Box-folder 42-2261)
    - General Education Board, 1938-40 (2 folders) (Box-folder 42-2262 to 42-2263)
    - General Education Board, 1939-46 (Box-folder 42-2264)
    - Glee Club, 1942 (Box-folder 42-2265)
    - Governor's Personnel Survey Staff, 1936-37 (Box-folder 42-2266)
    - Graduate Degrees (in Engineering), 1936 (Box-folder 42-2267)
    - Graduate Programs & Degrees, Committee on, 1940-41 (Box-folder 42-2268)
    - Graduate Work, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 42-2269)
    - Greenhouses, 1939-40 (Box-folder 42-2270)
    - Grounds Improvements, 1933-on (Box-folder 42-2271)
    - Guidance, Placement, etc., 1939 (Box-folder 42-2272)
    - H - Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box-folder 42-2273)
    - Heat & Power - Coal/F.Q. Saunders, 1942-44 (Box-folder 42-2274)
    - Hester (T.G.) Case, 1941 (Box-folder 42-2275)
    - Higher Instituting (Stauffer Report, etc.), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 42-2276)
    - Highways, Dept. of, 1941 (Box-folder 42-2277)
    - Hodges, Leroy, Managing Director, State COC, 1928-32 (Box-folder 42-2278)
    - Home Economics, 1937-38 (Box-folder 42-2279)
    - Home Economics, 1939 (Box-folder 43-2280)
    - Home Econ Dormitory, 1943-46 (Box-folder 43-2281)
    - Home Econ & D4 Equipment Quotations, 1940 (Box-folder 43-2282)
    - Teachers of Home Econ. & Vocational Agriculture, 1938-41 (Box-folder 43-2283)
    - Homestead Houses, 1930s (Box-folder 43-2284)
    - Honor System, Report of Joint Committee to Make Survey of, 1929 (Box-folder 43-2285)
    - Horticultural, 1944 (Box-folder 43-2286)
    - Horticulture/State Horticultural Society, 1939-41 (Box-folder 43-2287)
    - Hospital/Hospital Insurance Correspondence, 1940 (Box-folder 43-2288)
    - Houses, Mailboxes, Miscellaneous, 1931-34 (Box-folder 43-2289)
    - Humbert, R. L., 1942 (Box-folder 43-2290)
    - Information Memoranda, 1942 (Box-folder 43-2291)
    - Institute of Rural Affairs, 1929-33 (Box-folder 43-2292)
    - Instruction - Unit Costs, 1932-35 (Box-folder 43-2293)
    - Insurance, 1925-37 (Box-folder 43-2294)
      - Estimated Value of V.T. Campus Buildings.
      - Personal Effects Insurance on Students Living in Barracks.
      - Professor's Dwellings.
    - Letters from Insurance Companies, 1936 (Box-folder 43-2295)
    - Insurance & Bonds 1284-F, 1938-39 (Box-folder 43-2296)
    - Insurance & Bonds 1284-F, 1939-40 (Box-folder 43-2297)
    - Inventory, 1933 (Box-folder 43-2298)
    - Inventories/S.A.B. F.D.R.&H/H.E.R./President of, 1939 (Box-folder 43-2299)
    - Land Use, 1938 (Box-folder 43-2300)
    - Legislation, 1935-36 (Box-folder 43-2301)
    - Legislature, 1932 (Box-folder 43-2302)
      - Virginia Water Protection Act.
    - Library/Annual Reports, 1935-37 (Box-folder 43-2303)
    - Library Committee, 1941 (Box-folder 43-2304)
    - Livestock Loan, 1937 (Box-folder 43-2305)
    - Lynchburg College Cooperative Project, 1932-33 (Box-folder 43-2306)
    - M-Miscellaneous, 1933 (Box-folder 43-2307)
    - Mailboxes for Students, 1934-35 (Box-folder 43-2308)
    - Mailing Lists (Lists on Addressograph Plates), 1929-34 (Box-folder 43-2309)
    - Map & Directory Cards, R.H. McNeil (Box-folder 43-2310)
      - Detailed Map of V.P.I. Campus in 1930s.
    - Mary Baldwin College, 1938-39 (Box-folder 43-2311)
    - Mary Baldwin College, 1938-40 (Box-folder 43-2312)
    - Medals/Cincinnati/Sons of American Revolution/US Coast Artillery, 1944-45 (Box-folder 43-2313)
    - Meetings/Guest Groups/Conferences, Short Courses, 1935-40 (Box-folder 43-2314)
    - Merchant Marine Training School, 1932 (Box-folder 43-2315)
    - Merger with Radford College, 1944 (Box-folder 43-2316)
    - Mess Hall, 1942 (2 folders) (Box-folder 43-2317 to 43-2317A)
    - Methodist Conference, 1946 (Box-folder 43-2318)
    - Military-Requests to be Excused, 1934 (Box-folder 43-2319)
    - Name Change, 1944 (Box-folder 43-2320)
    - National Industrial Recovery Act (Box-folder 43-2321)
      - Summarized general Information of Dormitory Project for Students and Low Income Faculty.
    - National Conference on Rural Education, 1936-37 (Box-folder 44-2322)
      - House Bill-H.R. 13021.
    - National Education Association, 1933 (Box-folder 43-2323)
    - National Industrial Recovery Act, 1933 (Box-folder 43-2324)
      - Aerial Photo of V.P.I. Campus.
      - Federal Loan Application, Expected Expenditures.
    - National Recovery Administration, 1933 (Box-folder 44-2325)
    - N.R.A. Compliance, Exemption/Census Reports, 1934-35 (Box-folder 44-2326)
    - National Research Council, 1923-36 (Box-folder 44-2327)
    - National Research Council, 1942 (Box-folder 44-2328)
    - Nautical School for Merchant Marine Training #1, 1930-1941 (Box-folder 44-2329)
    - Nautical School for Merchant Marine Training #2, 1930-1941 (Box-folder 44-2330)
    - National Youth Administration Form Letters, 1934-35 (Box-folder 44-2331)
    - N.Y.A., 1935-38 (Box-folder 44-2332)
    - N.Y.A./Correspondence/Richmond, 1935-38 (Box-folder 44-2332A)
    - Correspondence-NYA & Student Aid, 1935-40 (Box-folder 44-2333)
    - National Youth Administration Official Corr., 1936 (Box-folder 44-2334)
    - National Youth Administration, 1937 (Box-folder 44-2335)
    - National Youth Administration Correspondence, 1938 (Box-folder 44-2336)
    - N.Y.A., 1938-40 (2 folders) (Box-folder 44-2337 to 44-2337A)
    - N.Y.A. Richmond, 1939-42 (Box-folder 44-2338)
    - N.Y.A., 1940-41 (Box-folder 44-2339)
    - N.Y.A. & College Jobs for the Year, 1940-41 (Box-folder 44-2340)
    - N.Y.A., 1941-42 (2 folders) (Box-folder 44-2341 to 44-2341A)
    - National Youth Administration Correspondence, 1942 (Box-folder 44-2342)
    - N.Y.A., 1942-43 (Box-folder 44-2343)
    - N.Y.A. Payroll, 1935-36 (Box-folder 44-2344)
    - N.Y.A. Payrolls, 1935-36 (Box-folder 44-2344A)
    - N.Y.A. Payroll, 1936-37 (Box-folder 44-2345)
    - N.Y.A. Payroll, 1937-38 (Box-folder 44-2346)
    - N.Y.A. Payroll, 1938-39 (Box-folder 44-2347)
    - N.Y.A. Payroll, 1940-41 (Box-folder 44-2348)
    - N.Y.A. Payroll, 1941-42 (Box-folder 45-2349)
    - N.Y.A. Proposed Work Plan, 1941-42 (Box-folder 45-2350)
    - N.Y.A. Work Plan, etc., 1942-43 (Box-folder 44-2351)
    - N.Y.A. Working, 1940-41 (Box-folder 45-2352)
    - N.Y.A. Worksheet, 1940-41 (Box-folder 45-2353)
    - Naval ROTC & Marine School, 1932-1940 (Box-folder 45-2354)
      - Letter to Navy Rear Admiral Nimitz.
      - Establishment of Naval Reserves Officers' Training Corp. Units.
      - H.R. 8612 Congressional Bill.
    - Newman, Walter S., 1941 (Box-folder 45-2355)
    - Norfolk Branch, 1941 (Box-folder 45-2356)
    - Nutrition, 1939-40 (Box-folder 45-2357)
    - Office of Government Reports, 1941 (Box-folder 45-2358)
    - Office of the President, 1928-34 (Box-folder 45-2359)
    - Office of the President, 1935-41 (Box-folder 45-2360)
    - Old Dominion Boys State, 1942 (Box-folder 45-2361)
    - Omnicron Delta Kappa (ODK) Society, 1937 (Box-folder 45-2362)
    - Organ AUD - Administration Building, 1935-41 (Box-folder 45-2363)
      - Hammond Organ Brochure.
    - Organizations, 1930-36 (Box-folder 45-2364)
    - Orientation Exercises & Programs, 1920-37 (Box-folder 45-2365)
    - Orientation Week, 1937-39 (Box-folder 45-2366)
    - Payrolls - College Students, 1935-36 (Box-folder 45-2367)
    - Penn, Col. J.E./Memorial, 1945 (Box-folder 45-2368)
    - Personnel Affidavit, 1942 (2 folders) (Box-folder 45-2369 to 44-2369A)
    - Personnel Policies, 1936 (Box-folder 45-2370)
    - Personnel Requirements, 1942 (Box-folder 45-2371)
    - Ph.D. Degree, 1936-38 (Box-folder 45-2372)
    - "Physical Culture" Fund, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 45-2373)
    - Physical Fitness Program, 1942 (Box-folder 45-2374)
    - Pittsylvania County Tobacco Growers Club/J.R. Hutcheson, 1938 (Box-folder 45-2375)
    - Posters, 1934-35 (Box-folder 45-2376)
    - Power Plant Addition Wiley & Wilson, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 45-2377)
    - Pre-Med Studies, 1940 (Box-folder 45-2378)
    - President's Annual Report, 1933 (Box-folder 45-2379)
    - President's Loan Fund, 1939-46 (Box-folder 46-2380)
    - Priddy, Lawrence, 1922 (Box-folder 46-2381)
    - Priddy, Lawrence, 1924 (Box-folder 46-2382)
    - Priddy, L., 1930 (Box-folder 46-2383)
    - Priddy, L., 1932 (Box-folder 46-2384)
    - Priddy, Lawrence, 1934 (Box-folder 46-2385)
    - Progressive Educational Association, 1932 (Box-folder 46-2386)
    - Prospective Students, 1934-35 (Box-folder 46-2387)
    - Public Service, 1935 (Box-folder 46-2388)
      - Progress report: Society for the promotion of engineering education.
    - Public Service of Dept. VPI, 1935 (Box-folder 46-2389)
      - "Ten years of Agricultural Engineering Service."
    - Quarterly Examinations, Fall 1932-33 (Box-folder 46-2390)
    - Quarters 1-2-3, 1933-34 (Box-folder 46-2391)
    - Quarters 1-2-3, 1934-35 (Box-folder 46-2392)
    - Quarter 1-2-3, 1935-36 (Box-folder 46-2393)
    - Quarters 1-2-3, 1936-37 (Box-folder 46-2394)
    - Replies to Questionnaire January 6, 1937 (Box-folder 46-2395)
    - Radio Committee, 1929-32 (Box-folder 46-2396)
    - Consolidation of Colleges - Radford-VPI Merger, 1943-44 (Box-folder 46-2397)
    - Radford-VPI Merger, 1943-44 (Box-folder 46-2398)
    - Radford-VPI Merger, 1944 (Box-folder 46-2399)
    - Radio Talks, 1939 (Box-folder 46-.2400)
    - Refund of Fees, Exemptions, etc., 1937 (Box-folder 46-2401)
    - Regional Research Lab, 1938 (Box-folder 46-2402)
    - Registration, October 16, 1940 (Box-folder 46-2403)
    - Registration Forms & Procedure, 1942 (Box-folder 46-2404)
    - Registration, January 4, 1943-44 (Box-folder 46-2405)
    - Relocation of Route #8, 1941-42 (Box-folder 46-2406)
    - Reorganization, 1943 (Box-folder 46-2407)
    - Request for Regional Research Laboratory Authorization In the Agricultural Adjustment Act, 1938 (Box-folder 46-2408)
    - Requisitions, 1935 (Box-folder 46-2409)
    - Research Foundation, Inc., 1940s (Box-folder 46-2410)
    - Retirement Income & Group Insurance, 1936-38 (Box-folder 46-2411)
    - Retirement Plans, 1936 (Box-folder 46-2412)
    - Retirement Plans, 1938 (Box-folder 47-2413)
    - Retirement Problems (Current Correspondence), 1938-40 (Box-folder 47-2414)
    - Retirement Plans, 1935 (Box-folder 47-2415)
    - Retirement Study, 1937 (Box-folder 47-2416)
    - Richmond - Conferences, Miscellaneous, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 47-2417)
    - ROTC Association of the US, 1931-33 (Box-folder 47-2418)
    - ROTC-Pros & Cons, World Peace, etc., 1931-33 (Box-folder 47-2419)
    - ROTC, 1934-36 (Box-folder 47-2420)
    - ROTC, 1937-41 (Box-folder 47-2421)
    - ROTC, 1941-42 (Box-folder 47-2422)
    - Scholarships, 1936 (Box-folder 47-2423)
    - Scholarships/Peninsular Base Section, 1945 (Box-folder 47-2424)
    - Science Advisory Board, 1935 (Box-folder 47-2425)
    - Senior Privilege Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 47-2426)
    - Sewer Estimates for Town of Blacksburg, 1938-40 (Box-folder 47-2427)
    - Shafer Court Case, 1932-33 (Box-folder 47-2428)
    - Sigma XI, 1940 (Box-folder 47-2429)
    - Museum (C. Bascom Slemp), 1939 (Box-folder 47-2430)
      - Slemp Museum - exact reproduction of early Settler homes in Southwest Virginia (miniatures), 1939
    - Smith (Captain John) Property, 1932 (Box-folder 47-2431)
    - Soil Conservation & Domestic Allotment Act, 1936-37 (Box-folder 47-2432)
    - Southern Assoc. of Colleges - Financial Report, 1933 (Box-folder 47-2433)
      - Staff and faculty count and salary.
      - List of graduates who went to graduate school and list of schools where they went. List of who received advanced degrees.
      - Academic department listing, and number of students and faculty.
    - Misc.-Southern Association of Colleges, Tax Report, 1933 (Box-folder 47-2434)
    - Southern Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools, 1936-41, n.d. (2 folders) (Box-folder 47-2435 to 47-2436)
    - Min. of the Annual Mtg of the Southern Conference, 1924-1929 (Box-folder 47-2437)
    - Min. of the Annual Mtg of the Southern Conference, 1929-1939 (Box-folder 47-2438)
    - Southern Conference, 1936-38 (Box-folder 47-2439)
    - Southern Conference (Athletic), 1937 (Box-folder 47-2440)
      - Southern conference constitution and by-laws.
    - Southwestern Council on Internal Relations, 1931-38 (Box-folder 47-2441)
    - Special Documents, 1943 (Box-folder 47-2442)
    - Stage Equipment, 1937-38 (Box-folder 47-2443)
    - Stahl Case, 1934-35 (Box-folder 47-2444)
    - Standards for Colleges, 1939 (Box-folder 47-2445)
    - State Building Committee, 1944-45 (Box-folder 47-2446)
    - State Highway Commission, 1929-35 (Box-folder 47-2447)
    - State Institutions of Higher Learning, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 47-2448)
    - Stauffer, Dr. Wm. H., 1934-35 (Box-folder 48-2449)
    - Summer Meetings, 1937 (Box-folder 48-2450)
    - Student Activities Building, 1937-1943 (Box-folder 48-2451)
    - Aid for Students, 1933-38 (Box-folder 48-2452)
    - Student Aid, 1939-40 (Box-folder 48-2453)
    - Student Aid - Waiterships, 1935-40 (Box-folder 48-2454)
    - Student Aid - College Jobs, 1936-37 (Box-folder 48-2455)
    - Student Aid - Departmental Requests, 1936-39 (Box-folder 48-2456)
    - Student Aid, Letters of Recommendation for, 1938-40 (Box-folder 48-2457)
    - Student Aid - Departmental Requests, 1939-43 (Box-folder 48-2458)
    - Student Employment Lists, 1939-40 (Box-folder 48-2459)
    - Student Expenses, 1931-34 (Box-folder 48-2460)
    - Financial Aid for Students, 1941-42 (Box-folder 48-2461)
    - Requests for Financial Aid for Students, 1942-43 (Box-folder 48-2462)
    - Student Forum-National Survey of Higher Education & Selective Service, 1941 (Box-folder 48-2463)
    - Student Life-Barracks Customs-Rat System, 1932 (Box-folder 48-2464)
    - Student Loans, 1934 (Box-folder 48-2465)
    - Student Personnel/Guidance, etc., 1928-35 (Box-folder 48-2466)
      - Student quality credit averages, 1934-1935
      - Corps of cadets petition for improved mess hall conditions-January 31, 1934.
      - New student statistics for 1926-1927.
    - Student Records, 1929-38 (Box-folder 48-2467)
    - Student Records, 1938-43 (Box-folder 48-2468)
    - Students, 1932-36 (Box-folder 48-2469)
    - Correspondence - Student, 1935-40 (Box-folder 48-2470)
    - Students' Finance Board, 1935-36 (Box-folder 48-2471)
      - Cost sheet for publication of "The Virginia Tech."
      - Survey results of high schools regarding college publications.
    - Student Placement Office/William C. Johnson, Jr., 1941 (Box-folder 48-2472)
    - Students Protective Association, 1932 (Box-folder 48-2473)
    - Student Welfare Committee, 1941-44 (Box-folder 48-2474)
    - Subsistence Homesteading, 1934 (Box-folder 49-2475)
    - Summer Quarter, 1926-36 (Box-folder 49-2476)
      - Professor list and salaries.
      - Student statistics for summer of 1930.
    - Summer Quarter, 1937-41 (Box-folder 49-2477)
    - Summer Quarter, 1942 (Box-folder 49-2478)
    - Swimming Pool, 1932-34 (Box-folder 49-2479)
    - Teaching Loads - Quarters 1-2-3, 1932-33 (Box-folder 49-2480)
      - Course numbers, numbers of students, and professsors.
    - University Club, 1935-1944 (Box-folder 49-2481)
    - Teachers' Agencies, 1934 (Box-folder 49-2482)
    - Teas for Faculty Wives, 1938-42 (Box-folder 49-2483)
    - Telegrams, 1932-36 (Box-folder 49-2484)
    - Telegrams, 1937 (Box-folder 49-2485)
    - Tennessee Valley Association (TVA), 1933 (Box-folder 49-2487)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1932-34 (Box-folder 49-2488)
    - TVA, 1933 (Box-folder 49-2489)
    - TVA, 1933-34 (2 folder) (Box-folder 49-2490 to 49-2491)
    - TVA-Electrical Jobs, etc., 1934 (Box-folder 49-2492)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1933-37 (Box-folder 49-2493)
    - TVA, 1937-38 (Box-folder 49-2494)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1942 (Box-folder 49-2495)
    - Trades & Industrial Education, 1936 (Box-folder 49-2496)
    - Travel Vouchers, 1928-32 (Box-folder 49-2497)
    - Unified Program for Education in VA & VA Policy, 1931-39 (Box-folder 49-2498)
    - U.S. Biological Survey - Game Management, 1942-45 (Box-folder 49-2499)
    - USDA Graduate School/Lectures & Discussions, 1939 (Box-folder 49-2500)
    - University Club, 1933-34 (Box-folder 49-2501)
    - Veterinarian Medical School, 1939 (Box-folder 49-2502)
    - VA Academy of Science - Planning Committee, 1940 (Box-folder 49-2503)
    - Lists of Virginia Industries, 1942 (Box-folder 49-2504)
    - Virginia Manufacturers, 1936 (Box-folder 49-2505)
    - V.P.I. in Bluefield, Lynchburg, Norfolk, Richmond, 1932-34 (Box-folder 50-2506)
    - Financial Reports of VPI Publications, 1933-34 (Box-folder 50-2507)
    - VPI University Club, Director, 1939-41 (Box-folder 50-2508)
    - VA Program in Relation to Tennessee Valley Aut., 1933-34 (Box-folder 50-2509)
    - Virginia Social Science Association, 1929-34 (Box-folder 50-2510)
    - The Virginia Tech, Editor, 1941 (Box-folder 50-2511)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1940 (Box-folder 50-2512)
    - Virginia Wildlife Research Program, 1935-36 (Box-folder 50-2513)
    - Wages Adjustment, 1941-42 (Box-folder 50-2514)
    - Water & Sewers, 1930-44 (Box-folder 50-2515)
    - Well Drilling, 1941-42 (2 folders) (Box-folder 50-2516 to 50-2517)
    - Whitethorne Animal Husb. Department, 1937 (Box-folder 50-2518)
    - Women Students, Admission of, 1934-35 (Box-folder 50-2519)
    - W.P.A. (Beautification Project), 1935-39 (Box-folder 50-2520)
    - Works Projects Administration, 1941-42 (Box-folder 50-2521)
    - W.P.A. (Disaster Project), 1942 (Box-folder 50-2522)
    - Yenching University - China, 1935-37 (Box-folder 50-2523)
    - YMCA, 1932-36 (Box-folder 50-2524)
    - YMCA, 1934 (Box-folder 50-2525)
- Series 7: Defense and the War Effort, 1940-1945
  - Miscellaneous A, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 50-2526)
  - Air Raid Orders for Schools (Box-folder 50-2527)
  - Air Raid Shelters, 1941-42 (Box-folder 50-2528)
  - Air Raid Warden-Questions & Answers February 3, 1942 (Box-folder 50-2529)
  - Aircraft Warning Service, 1941-42 (Box-folder 50-2530)
  - Aircraft Warning System, December 10, 1941 (Box-folder 50-2531)
  - Army & Navy Directives, etc., 1944 (Box-folder 50-2532)
  - Army Public Relations (Box-folder 50-2533)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 50-2534)
  - Bedford Co.-Defense Committee, J.T. Davidson, Jr., 1942 (Box-folder 50-2535)
  - Blackouts, 1941 (Box-folder 50-2536)
  - Blackouts, August 1941 (Box-folder 50-2537)
  - Minutes from Blacksburg Civilian Defense Council, 1941 (Box-folder 50-2538)
  - B'burg & VPI Defense Committee-J.M. Barringer, 1942 (Box-folder 50-2539)
  - Bomb Tests (Report of) on Materials & Structures (Box-folder 50-2540)
  - British Cities at War, 1941 (Box-folder 50-2541)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 50-2542)
  - Cities & the National Defense Program, May 1941 (Box-folder 50-2543)
  - Citizens' Defense Corps, 1942 (Box-folder 50-2544)
  - Citizens Road League of Virginia Tech, 1936 (Box-folder 50-2545)
  - Civilian Defense, 1941-43 (Box-folder 50-2546)
  - Purchasing Civilian Defense Insignia, 1941-42 (Box-folder 50-2547)
  - Civilian Protection, 1941 (Box-folder 50-2548)
  - College Credit for Military Experience & Other, 1944 (Box-folder 50-2549)
  - Commodity Distribution Committee/J. Fulmer Bright, Administration, 1942 (Box-folder 50-2550)
  - Commodity Distribution Bulletins, 1942 (2 folders) (Box-folder 51-2551 to 51-2552)
  - Advisory Commission to Council of Nat'l Defense, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2553)
  - County Defense Committees: Bland Carroll, Craig, Floyd, Franklin, Fries, Galax, Giles, 1941-42 (Box-folder 51-2554)
  - County Defense Committees: Grayson, Montgomery, Pulaski, Radford, Roanoke, Roanoke (city), Wythe, 1941-42 (Box-folder 51-2555)
  - Miscellaneous D, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 51-2556)
  - Defense Contract Service, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2557)
  - Defense Housing Coordination, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2558)
  - Local Defense Organization, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2559)
  - Defense Measures, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2560)
  - The Defense Program (Box-folder 51-2561)
  - Defense Savings Stamps, 1941-42 (Box-folder 51-2562)
  - Defense Training Courses, 1941-42 (Box-folder 51-2563)
  - Miscellaneous E, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 51-2564)
  - Misc.-Executive Bulletin, Defense Training Act., etc., 1941-42 (Box-folder 51-2565)
  - Fire Defense, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2566)
  - Fire Mobilization Committee, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2567)
  - First Aid, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2568)
  - Flight Training (Navy) CAA, 1943-44 (Box-folder 51-2569)
  - Gas, Protection Against, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2570)
  - Glass & Glass Substitutes (Box-folder 51-2571)
  - Home Nursing Classes, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2572)
  - Homes Registration, 1941-42 (Box-folder 51-2573)
  - Industrial Buildings, Protection of (Box-folder 51-2574)
  - Local Defense Committees-Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2575)
  - Local Information Committees (Box-folder 51-2576)
  - Manual of the Senate and House of Delegates, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2577)
  - National Defense, 1940 (Box-folder 51-2578)
  - National Defense, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2579)
  - National Defense Bulletins, 1941 (Box-folder 51-2580)
  - National Defense-Selective Service, etc., 1942 (2 folders) (Box-folder 51-2581 to 51-2582)
  - Naval Aviation Training Program, 1943 (Box-folder 51-2583)
  - Naval Operating Base, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2584)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1924-1944 (Box-folder 51-2585)
  - OCD, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 51-2587)
    - Role of Boy Scouts and relationship between Office of Civiian Defnse
    - Bill of Rights Day publication
  - OCD Newsletter, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2586)
  - Price, Gov. James H., 1940-1942 (Box-folder 51-2588)
    - Proclamation extending daylight savings to additional areas in order to garner additional energy for national defense purposes
  - Public Proclamation, 1942 (Box-folder 51-2589)
  - Radford Regional Defense Council, 1940 (Box-folder 51-2590)
  - Minutes from Radford Regional Defense Council, 1941 (Box-folder 52-2591)
  - Readjusting Salaries, Bonus & Accelerated Program, 1942-43 (Box-folder 52-2592)
  - Report to the Nation, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2593)
  - Safety Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2594)
  - Sanitation Reports/Health Measures, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2595)
  - Selective Training Act & Selective Service, 1940-41 (Box-folder 52-2596)
  - Tire Rationing, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2597)
  - Transmittal Memoranda, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2598)
  - United Service Organization (USO) (Box-folder 52-2599)
  - The US Citizens Defense Corps (Box-folder 52-2600)
  - Virginia Civil Defense, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2601)
  - Virginia Civil Defense-Informational Memoranda, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2602)
  - Virginia Defense Council, Minutes, 1941 (Box-folder 52-2603)
  - Virginia Defense Council, 1941 (Box-folder 52-2604)
  - Virginia Defense Council (Box-folder 52-2605)